What is this?

This Java program was made for the sole purpose of separating a single MIDI
Track into 4 channels for use with Mechbass, made by James McVay.

For more information about MIDI Files and their structure visit
http://www.ccarh.org/courses/253/handout/smf/

===

How do I use the Program?

1) Find a MIDI file you want to play on Mechbass. This file MUST be a MIDI
File.

2) Open the program.

3) Loading the File:
GUI: Click the "Load" button, or go to <File> --> <Open MIDI File>.
Command Line: <DOCUMENTATION ON HOW TO USE COMING SOON!>

4) Choose a bass track from the drop down menu.

5) Solving the File:
GUI: Click the "Solve" button, or go to <File> --> <Solve MIDI File>.
Command Line: <DOCUMENTATION ON HOW TO USE COMING SOON!>

6) Saving the File:
GUI: Click the "Save" button, or go to <File> --> <Save MIDI File>.
Command Line: <DOCUMENTATION ON HOW TO USE COMING SOON!>

You should now have a MIDI file that can be played on Mechbass.

===

Playback:

You can play the MIDI file at any point by pressing the "Play" button. You can
also use <Playback> --> <Play>.
!! CAUTION !!
As of right now, you SHOULD NOT "play" a file while a file is already
playing. Doing so will play the file again from the start while the 
current file is still playing (i.e. you'll play the file on top of 
itself).

You can pause the MIDI file at any point by pressing the "Pause" button. You 
can resume MIDI File playback from the paused point by Playing the MIDI File 
again.

You can stop the MIDI file at any point by pressing the "Stop" button. You can
also use <Playback> --> <Stop>. This will stop playback and bring the MIDI File
playback position to the beginning.

You can also Shift the notes in the MIDI File up or down an octave by using
<Playback> --> <Shift Octave Up> or <Playback> --> <Shift Octave Down>.